ILGWU Justice Photographs 5780/102 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- International (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Includes: Executive VP Wilbur Daniels meets with Dr. Paulo Santos, sub-chair of cabinet of the Ministry of Labor in Brazil and interpreter Henry Bagley at ILGWU General Office, 3/11/??; VP Heroch Mendelsund, representing US Garment and Textile Unions at 30th anniversary convention of Zensen Domei, the Japanese counterpart, addresses delegates, with Zensen President Tadanobu Usami and Eiko Igasaki, Secretary of the Textile Workers' Asian Regional organization, who acted as translator, Tokyo, 10/1/75; Visiting the new clinic in Ramat Chen, Israel named after late VP Moe Falikman, former Cutters Manager, are Malka Portugal of Histadrut, Joshua Levy - former Treasurer of Histadrut, Mrs. Stulberg, Honorary President Louis Stulberg, Mrs. Abe Dolgen, Mrs. Falikman, VP Dolgen - Local 10 Manager, and Dr. Franz Brull - head of the Department of Psychiatry at Tel Aviv University, 12/15/75; Getting ready to send off $15,000 worth of clothing to children in Portugal are VP Sol Greene - Manager of Local 155, Portuguese Socialist Francisco Salgado, President Sol C. Chaikin, Henry Proshen - acting manager of Local 105, and VP Edward Schneider - Local 91 Manager, 4/15/76; President Sol C. Chaikin welcomes former West German Chancellor Willy Brandt to a reception in his honor given by the Social Democrats, USA, with Carl Gershman - Executive Director of SD, USA, and Bayard Rustin, National Chairman, 3/15/77; Visiting Turkish Unionists meet with Local 23-25 Assistant Manager Jay Mazur with former ILGWU official Maida Springer Kemp, New York, 4/1/77; President Sol C. Chaikin welcomes Portuguese Premier Mario Soares to reception in his honor sponsored by the ILGWU and Social Democrats USA, with SD National Chairman Bayard Rustin and Israeli UN Ambassador Chaim Herzog, 4/22/77; President Sol C. Chaikin meets with visiting trade unionists, who come mainly from Africa and Latin America, 5/15/77; ILG's Henoch Mendelsund took an active role in the deliberations of the International Labor Organization's Conference with R.S. Milne, ILO Secretary General, and J Reynaut, Deputy Secretary General, Geneva, Switzerland, Dec. 1980; Polish strikers hoist strike leader Lech Walesa on their shoulders at the Lenin Shipyard in Gdansk, Poland, Oct. 1980; The ILGWU delegation joined with the American Federation of Teachers, Social Democrats USA, and other groups at a reception honoring AFL-CIO European Representative Irving Brown, with SOUSA Executive Director Rita Freedman, President Chaikin, A. Philip Randolph Institute Chairman Bayard Rustin (who's also SD National Chairman), Brown, and AFT President Albert Shanker, 11/17/81; VP Edward Schneider, Director of International Relations Department, greets delegation of visiting trade unionists, Oct. 1981; President Sol C. Chaikin was at head of march during a demonstration part of worldwide show of support for solidarity unionists, with Irena Kirkland, wife of AFL-CIO President, and ILGWU Legislative Director Evelyn Dubrow, Washington, DC, 12/30/81; Town East Garment Factory Ltd., Jan. 1983
- International (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Includes: The President of the Turkish Federation of Trade Unions, Halil Tunc visits with General Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton, with Henoch Mendelsund - ILGWU International Relations Director, and Ed Wesinger of the Asian-American Free Labor Institute (AAFCI), new York City, no date; At press conference following joint meeting of American and Japanese garment and textile unionists, ILGWU Secretary-treasurer Shelley Appleton call for extension and strengthening of the Multifiber Textile Arrangement, 1977; Meeting, no date; Outlining effects of imports on US garment industry to Zensen Domei delegation is General Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton with ILGWU Research Director Lazare Teper, ILG International Relations Director Henoch Mendelsund, ILG Executive VP Wilbur Daniels, ACTWU President Murray Finley, ACTWU Secretary-Treasurer Jacob Sheinkman and ACTWU Sr. Executive VP Sol Stein, no date; AFL-CIO President George Meany, Secretary-Treasurer Lane Kirkland, and US Labor Secretary Ray Marshall joined delegations from ILGWU, and ACTWU and Zensen Domei at reception held for the Japanese Unionists, no date; General Secretary-Treasurer Appleton presents a gift on behalf of the ILGWU and the ACTWU to Tadanobu Usani, President of Zensen Domei, 12/1/77; International Relations Director Henoch Mendelsund and Secretary-Treasurer Appleton, 12/1/77; Carl Gershman, Executive Director of Social Democrats USA, welcomes Italian Social Democratic leader Pier Luigi Romita to a luncheon on his behalf with ILGWU General Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton, 12/15/78; The New York Hilton at Rockefeller Center; Photo of poor family, 1/1/79; The leaders of Egyptian Textile and Garment Union were welcomed last month at the ILGWU General Office, with Kemal Riad Talin Salama - VP of the General Trade Union of Textile and Spinning Workers of Egypt, ILGWU General Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton, President Aly Mohamed Dofda, President Sol C. Chaikin, Fathi Hamad bad Rabou el-Adawy - VP, Executive VP Wilbur Daniels and Henoch Mendelsund - Director of the ILGWU International Relations Department, 12/1/78; Modern garment factory in Somerang, Indonesia, 1/1/79; Street scene I Bandung, Indonesia, 1/1/79; Horse and cart in Surakarta, Indonesia, Indonesia, 1/1/79; A knitting mill in Bandung, Indonesia, 1/1/79; VP Mazur with AAFCI Executive Director Morris Palladino, Dan Newsom, Country Program Director of AAFCI, and Garment Workers Federation President Marjuki, 1/1/79; Three man, no date
- International, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 4, Folder 15)
- International (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Includes: Sol C. Chaikin greeted Andre Bergeron - the Secretary General of the French Labor Federation, Force Ouvriere (FO), with Patrick J. O'Farrell, Executive Director of the African-American Labor Center, VP Jay Mazur - Local 23-25 Manager, Antoine Laval - an aide to Bergeron, VP Edward Schneider - Sportswear Joint Board General Manager, Jay Lovestone - ILGWU International Affairs consultant, Harry Van Arsdale - President of the New York City Central Labor Council, Henoch Mendelsund - Director of ILGWU International Relations Department, Irving Brown - AFL-CIO representative to European labor organizations, VP Sam Nemaizer - new York Cloak-Dress Joint Board General manager, Executive VP Wilbur Daniels, and VP Edward Kramer, New Jersey Region General manager, 1/17/79; Scene in Tavha Shirts plant, China, June 1979; Cutting department in Tavha Shirts plant, China, June 1979; Folding shirts by window light in Tavha Shirts plant, China, June 1979; Fashions in store window, China, June 1979; Working hard for low government-set wages, Tavah Shirts plant, China, June 1979; President Sol C. Chaikin was featured at an executive council meeting of the Inter-American Textile, Leather and Garment Workers Federation, with Mike Ruano - Local 415-475 manager, Anita Cofino - '415-475' Political Department, Gustavo Rodriguez - '415-475' President, Angel Cofino - exiled Cuban Labor leader, Carlos Bedoya - Secretary General of the IATLGWF, Enrique Miko - President of the Garment Workers Union in Argentina, and VP Edward Schneider -a member of the executive council, Miami, Sept. 1979; President Sol C. Chaikin confers with delegation of top Italian labor leaders, with Irving Brown - AFL-CIO representative in Europe, Henoch Mendelsund - Director of ILGWU International Relations Department, VP frank Longo - Local 89 manager and Santo Pernicone of the Italian American Labor Council, Oct. 1979; Andrei Sakharov is barred by a Soviet policeman from attending the trial of dissident Yuri Orlov, Moscow, Nov. 1979; The Kremlin, 1979; President Sol C. Chaikin lashes out at Soviet repression of dissident Andrei Sakharov at national press conference held January 30, with Tatyana and Yefrem Yankelovich, the scientist's daughter and son-in-law; President Sol C. Chaikin and top union officers confer with representatives of the Egyptian Federation of Labor, with Hassan Ead - Secretary-General for International Relations, Abu Bakr Gad Al Mawla, Treasurer, and Mustafa Ibrahim Mustafa - Assistant Treasurer, with Chaikin were General Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton, Executive Vice Presidents Wilbur Daniels and Frederick R. Siems, Henoch Mendelsund - Director of the ILGWU International Relations Department, VP Edward Schneider - General Manager of the Sportswear Joint Board, and Robert Richter - Program Officer of the African-American Labor Center
- International, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 4, Folder 17)
- International (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Includes: Soldiers of the 15th tank brigade of Afghan Armed Forces which was awarded by the Afghan Defense Ministry with honorary pendent "For Military Heroism", Kabul, Afghanistan, 1/18/80; At dedication of Louis Stulberg Hospital in Kfar Saba, Israel, are Dr. Chaim Doron - Director of Kupat Holim, the medical program of the Israeli Labor Federation, President Sol C. Chaikin, and Bebe Stulberg, widow of the former ILGWU President, July 1980; ILGWU delegation visiting Egyptian medical facility with trade unionist, including M. Galal Misbah - VP of MISR Spinning and Weaving Trade Union, and Sami Ezz Elarab, VP of General Trade Union of Textile and Spinning Workers, July 1980; Hungry children in Cambodia, Aug. 1980; Village in poverty, Cambodia, Aug. 1980; Poor family, Cambodia, Aug. 1980; Delegation at Caribbean unionists representing San Lucia, Barbados, Jamaica, and Trinidad visits the High School of Fashion Industries, with Principal Sol Baily, Agatha Chatterton and Elaine Jones of Barbados Workers Union, Clement Prospere - San Lucia Workers Union, Michele Brianes Program Coordinator - ILGWU International Relations Department, VP Edward Schneider - Sportswear General Manager and Director of the ILGWU International Relations Department, and Jack Heberle of the American Institute for Free Labor Development, 5/5/81; VP Edward Schneider, Sportswear General Manager and Director of the ILGWU International Relations Department Greek Caribbean Unionists at an ACTWU reception, New York, 5/5/81; VP Edward Schneider, Sportswear General Manager and Director of the ILGWU International Relations Department welcomes Caribbean Unionists to the ILGWU International Relations Department offices, 5/5/81; Agatha Chatterton of the Barbados Workers Unions, 5/5/81; Lois Carol, Manager Local 295 conducts a tour of Lady Carol cutting shop for Caribbean Unionists, Pittsburgh, PA, 5/5/81; VP Edward Schmeider with Egyptian trade union leaders at Mehalla El-Kubra textile apparel complex, with Sami Elarab - member of Parliament and VP of General trades Union of Textile and Spinning Workers, and Galal Misbah, associate member of Parliament and President of the Union at Mehalla, Oct. 1984
- International, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 4, Folder 19)
- International, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Italians (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Includes: Chaikin at meeting of Italian American Labor Council, no date; Chaikin speaking at meeting of Italian American Labor Council, no date; Italian American labor Council, no date; Chaikin and speaker at Italian American Labor Council, no date; Men at meeting, no date; Italian American Labor Council, no date; Italian American labor Council, no date; ILGWU Local #89 Collection Depot for Italian Earthquake Disaster, Jan. 1981; Demonstration of ILGWU Local 89, no date; Production Mens Guild of the Dress Industry give $1000.00 to Italian American Labor Council, Howard Molisani, President Herman Katy, Luigi Antonini-President, Morris Stortch, Al Bistner, John Geller, Andrew Mananara, GD Procopio, Charles Roven, Patsy Naturelli, Joseph Collura, 11/14/52; John Gelo and wife (?), no date; Unidentified man, no date; Award presented to William Green (President of AFL?), Luigi Antonini also present in this photo, no date (?); Gathering of people at Columbus House, Genoa, Italy, 1954; First-Vice President Luigi Antonini greets the tourist group of the Educational Committee of the of the Italian-American Labor Council at Idlewild Airport on the return from the one- month excursion in Italy, 6/21/54; First-Vice President Luigi Antonini, Jennie, and Vanni Montana reading inscription on monument to Emperor Aurelio Antonini, no date; Vanni Montana, Luigi Antonini and Jennie on their arrival at the airport in Rome, no date; Members of "Good-Will Tour" on the steps of the Capitol in Rome, no date; Luigi Antonini in factory, no date; Palermo Bount to open FDR Orphanage, friends and members of for 89, Guseppi Procopio - Secretary of the Italian American Labor Council and daughter Elvira, Mr. and Mrs. Luigi Antonini at LaGuardia airport leaving for Italy, no date; Isidore Breslow, William Schwartz, Zimmerman, Sal Noto, Moe Falikman, no date; Stulberg and Howard Molisani, no date; Luigi Antonini, no date; Luigi Antonini, no date; Lyndon B. Johnson and Molisani shake hands with Zimmerman, no date; Harry S. Truman and Harold Molisani, no date; Harold Molisani taking an oath, with Luigi Antonini; The United Italian American Labor Council presented its annual four Freedoms Award at a luncheon December 4 to Rep. Thomas P. O'Neill, the Massachusetts congressman who has been elected Speaker of the House of Representatives, with General Consul Alessandro Cortese DeBaris, ILGWU First-Vice President E. Howard Molisani - President of the IALC, ILGWU President Sol C. Chaikin, and New York Mayor Abraham Beame, 12/4/76; President Sol C. Chaikin presents AFL-CIO President George Meany with medal of appreciation form Italy's trade unions for relief assistance sent to earthquake victims in Northern Italy, 12/1/76
- Unity House/Diego Rivera Murals (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Includes: murals of annexation of Texas, IWW and Stamp Act, copy of 5780 PUBS #511 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 30
- Unity House Forest Park Post Cards (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Includes: photos of Forest Park Hotel in Forest Park [pre-1920], PA; surrounding buildings and wooded areas; recreational activities. Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 31
- Upper South Department (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Includes: Sol Chaikin discusses improvements with members at Appomattox Garment Co. in VA- 9/1/74; Business Agent Betsy Raymond shows her cutting skill at ILGWU Booth at Union Label Show- 9/15/74; Helen Turc and Edith Lawn- Local 106 members turning out handkerchiefs with Mary Ann Moore of Local 4 and Gene Connolly of Local 106 VP Wilbur Daniels- director of Master Agreements Department discusses negotiations with staff conference at Upper South Department's education center- with VP Sol Hoffman- Upper South Director- 11/15/74; ILGWU theater group from Baltimore in Philadelphia- Martin Rader, Lorraine Royster, Glenn Blanchard, Argentine Cheatham, Irene Perez, Nikki Jones, Arleen Jackson, Donna Rader, Marie Prunkl, Mary Vanlandingham, Albert Vanlandingham, Mary Sturdivant, Ruth Williams, and Sidney Cheatham- 12/15/74; Business Agent Buddy Sturm explains agreement to Jodi Sportswear employees in Fruitland, MD- with Upper South Organizing Director Jay Levine, John Downing, and Irene Chapman- 1/15/75; Coronet Casuals workers hold backpay checks- with Jay Levine, Cathy Powell, Charlotte Breeden, Pauline Queen, Madge Spigner, Rene Canady, Susie Wallop, John Downing and Geraldine Bashar- 2/1/76; Business Agent Angelo Giordano and Nelson Hill talking to Gloria Mfg. Employees in Newport News, VA- 3/15/75; strikers outside Gloria Mfg- 3/15/75; strikers outside Gloria Mfg- 3/15/75; Randolph Institute in Baltimore convention- with George Meany and Randolph- 6/75 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 32
- Upper South Department (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Includes: representatives of union negotiating and employer after contract signing- with VP Sol Hoffman 8/15/75; VP Sol Hoffman, Charles Sturm, and Stella Davis give opinion on imports; post-negotiations at Easter Isles' plant in Richlands and Grundy, VA- 9/15/75; Andy Andreone, Guinevere Banks and Arlene Jackson give opinion on imports; VP Wilbur Daniels open up meeting with VP Sol Hoffman and Evelyn Dubrow to discuss imports; VP Sol Hoffman- director of South Department gives Woodstock Mfg. Contract Norma George and Assistant Chairlady Norma Miller; after negotiations at Bristol Lingerie in VA are Peggy Talbert, Betty Smithson, Madge Gross, LaDonna Cassidy, Vivian Hickman, Bob Frank, Linda Deniable, Margaret Emmert, Barbara Wye, Maggie Malone, Ada Jakubic, Sol Hoffman, Lois Sullins and Martin Vest- 1/1/76; VP Sol Hoffman joins picket at A B uniform in Norfolk, VA- 1/1/76; Employer negotiators Irving Feldstein, Ray Frederick, Hank Depner face union Ronnie Wills, Virginia Ferguson, Jean Mills, VP Sol Hoffman, state director Mario Marcello, Mabel Hayes, Randy Carson, Virginia Maynard, Elizabeth Wiley for Huntington Industries in West Virginia- 4/1/76; VP Sol Hoffman gives check to Admiral Elmo "Bud" Zumwatt- 5/1/76; Upper South Organizing Director Jay Levine and organizer Martin Lesser discuss Lori Till case- 6/1/76; George Meany award is given to Lillie Stansbury- Local 256 in Frederick, MD with C.W. McNemar, Glenn Watts and George Atkins-6/15/76; Negotiations with Claire Frock with Sol Hoffman, Gladys Frommeyer, Janet Marsh, Ruth Shane, Agnes Eyler, Kathryn Bradshaw, Shirley Adkins, Roy Clabaugh, Jerry Moore and Calvin Saylor Maryland-Delaware State Director Harry Frankel hosts luncheon at United Togs plant in Sussex Blades, Delaware- 8/15/76; Ellen Smith, VP of ILGWU's Eastern Shore Area Council talks with people who visit ILGWU Booth at 22nd annual Labor Day Weekend Festival in Greenbelt, MD- 10/1/76; Melvin Bourne, administrator of ACTWU day care center chats with Upper South business agent Clara Gummer- 1/15/77; Mike Newman, Robert Farber, Jay Levine, and Jackson Moore celebrate union recognition at Athena Industries in Kingsport, TN- 3/1/77 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 33
- Upper South Department (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Includes: Local President Bessie Roy pins corsage on Florence Leonard at the 25th anniversary celebration of Baltimore Local 106- 11/15/59; bouquet of roses for Jane Burhams, first lady of Hagerstown, MD- 9/1/59; wife of State's LT. Governor A.E.S. Stephens sews first label into dress produced by Kenrose Mfg. Co. of Roanoke, VA- with LT. Governor Stephens, ILGWU VP Angela Bambace, Sherill Caldwell and Martin Vest- 3/1/61; David Dubinsky confers with Morris Glusnier and Alice Reca on picket line outside Kenrose Mfg. Co.- 7/1/60; strikers outside Classic Uniform of Baltimore- 7/15/65; a black man leads the picket line in song; black women picket and sing union songs outside Barclay Uniform Co. in Baltimore, MD- 8/15/65; Lari Anese Melton wears union outfit at fashion show by Local 563- 8/1/66; representing the union in negotiations with People's Company in Huntington, W. Virginia- Ruth Matthews, Joel Goolst, Upper South Organizing Director, Jerry Johnson, Glenn Mallot, Dorcus Watson, Donna Daniels, Evelyn Moses; photo of cutters; VP Angele Bambace is honored at dinner of Baltimore Community Relations Commission- 6/15/67; Upper South Department triennial conference in Washington D.C.- with Meany, Howard Molisani, Joel Goost, Angela Bambace works with Local 4 to start a day camp- 5/15/70; Evelyn Dubrow, Meany, Angela Bambace, Hattie Williams, and Clara Gummer paid a visit to General Office in NY to present plaque to President Louis Stulberg commemorating to 70th anniversary of ILGWU- 1/1/71; picket line against Dee-More Business Co.- 2/1/72; VP Angela Bambace honored as she retires with Wilbur Daniels and Jacob Edelman- 12/15/72; Local 4 members at Eutaw Manufacturing cast votes in Upper South Department elections- 4/1/74 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 34
- Welfare and Health Benefits Department (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Includes: Sol Chaikin presides over meeting of trustees of Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund at Unity House- with Louis Relnick- director of Welfare and Health Benefits- 9/8/76; William Shulman of Wolf and Shulman presents report on Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund with Louis Relnick, Louis Stulberg, and Ted Bernstein- assistant department director- 12/1/74 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 35
- Western States Region - California (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Includes: VP Samuel Otto, James Roosevelt, Manager Stenzor at LA rally; union label display; Garment Workers at LA Campaign Committee headquarters make contributions and pick up literature- 11/60; John Kennedy addresses a crowd in Hartford, CT- 12/15/60; proper use of fire fighting equipment is demonstrated by LA Bureau of Fire Prevention to Cloak Joint Board- with Bureau Inspector- R.H. Coleman and Joint Board Manager Isidor Stenzor- 4/1w5/60; Designers Local 452 and Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association signs contract with Harry LeCover- association press, Hyman Schatzberg- Local 452 president Phil Garb- assistant executive secretary, Cloak Joint Board manager Isidor Stenzor, Basil Feinberg, VP Samuel Otto and Jerome Reiner- 2/1/60; John Ulene- LA Dress and Sportswear Joint Board manager pickets with workers from Murray Millman-10/15/61; Retiree reception with manager John Ulene, co-chairlady Callie Williams, Dora Williams, Murray Kovitz; installation meeting of newly elected officers of LA Cloak locals 3/15/62; LA ILGers distribute leaflets-3/15/63; Isidor Stenzor, manager of LA Cloak Joint Board, VP Charles Zimmerman and Samuel Otto- 4/15/63; members of Chinatown office of San Francisco Joint Board are shown during English class- with Cornelius Wall- joint board manager and organizer Chao Wei Liang- 7/63; President Louis Stulberg addresses ILGers in LA-1/15/69 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 36
- Western States Region - California (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Includes: LA Cloak Joint Board committee negotiates contract renewal- Morris Silverstein, Basil Feinberg, Charles Nash, Isidor Stenzor, Samuel Otto, Theresa Oliver, Emma Goldman, Ben Kraus, Albert Axelrod, Moe Solomon, Abe Tankenson, Manuel Ponce, Mike Cristofaro, Sophie Siegel, Virginia King, Jennie Spallino- 5/1/15/64; San Francisco ILGers greet President Johnson in Bay City- business agent Myrtle M. Banks, Cornelius Wall and Thomas Pitts; David Dubinsky at meeting of ILGWU in LA- with VP Samuel Otto, Isidor Stenzor, Cornelius Wall- 12/1/64; Congressman James Roosevelt speaks at installation of LA Cloak Joint Board officers- Meyer Silverstein, Max. B. Wolf, VP Samuel Otto, Charles Nash, Isidor Stenzor- manager, Basil Feinberg, and Moe Solomon- 4/1/65; Geno picket Wayne Engel with gash on his face- 4/1/66; picketers outside Geno of California- 2/15/66; ILGWU organizer Pius Lee leads picket line at Marguerite Rubel shop in Chinatown- 4/1/68; picketers of Chic Lingeue with some Spanish signs; Mattie Jackson, new manager of San Francisco Joint Board- 9/1/70; Western States Director Cornelius Wall speaks with Basil Feinberg, Sam Schwartz, and Isidor Stenzor looking on as Dress and Sportswear Joint Board merges with Cloak Joint Board- 1/1/71; Mayor Thomas Bradley presents proclamation to VP Cornelius Wall- Western States Director- 8/1/73; SK and K workers in San Pedro, CA picket- 8/1/74; negotiating team explain terms of pact renewal with Messerman Sportswear in LA- 8/15/74; Julius Draznin- regional deputy director of NLRB speaks at Western States Region meeting in LA- 8/15/74; Cornelius Wall presents money to a woman; Edmund G. Brown, Jr. speaks at rally of ILGWU members- with Cornelius Wall, Max Wolf, Sigmund Arywitz, and Mervyn Dymally- 10/15/74; people distribute leaflets in LA Valley; striking workers at Great Chinese-American sewing Co. in San Francisco- 10/15/74 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 37